<section class="txtsrc"><p>Saturnus Iupiter; Saturnus Mars; Saturnus Sol; Saturnus Venus; Saturnus Mercurius; Saturnus Luna; Iuppiter Mars; Iupiter Sol; Iupiter Venus; Iupiter Mercurius; Iupiter Luna; Mars Sol; Mars Venus; Mars Mercurius; Mars Luna; Sol Venus; Sol Mercurius; Sol Luna; Venus Mercurius; Venus Luna; Mercurius Luna.</p>
<p>Ternaria 35<span class="note"><a aria-label="479" class="note txt" href="#n479"></a><small class="note" data-sign="479" id="n479"> Ternaria 35<span class="txt">]</span> Ternaria 35 <i class="txt">add. i. m. V</i></small></span>: Saturnus Iupiter Mars; Saturnus Iupiter Sol; Saturnus Iupiter Venus; Saturnus Iupiter Mercurius; Saturnus Iupiter Luna; Saturnus Mars Sol; Saturnus Mars Venus; Saturnus Mars Mercurius; Saturnus Mars Luna; Saturnus Sol Venus; Saturnus Sol Mercurius; Saturnus Sol Luna; Iuppiter Mars Sol; Iupiter Mars Venus; Iupiter Mars Mercurius; Iupiter Mars Luna; Iuppiter Sol Venus; Iupiter Sol Mercurius; Iupiter Sol Luna; Iuppiter Venus Mercurius; Iupiter Venus Luna; Iuppiter Mercurius Luna; Mars Sol Venus; Mars Sol Mercurius; Mars Sol Luna; Mars Venus Mercurius; Mars Venus Luna; Mars Mercurius Luna; Sol Venus Mercurius; Sol Venus Luna; Sol Mercurius Luna; Venus Mercurius Luna.</p>
<p>Quarternaria 35<span class="note"><a aria-label="480" class="note txt" href="#n480"></a><small class="note" data-sign="480" id="n480"> Quarternaria 35<span class="txt">]</span> Quarternaria 35 <i class="txt">add. i. m. V</i></small></span>: Saturnus Iupiter Mars Sol; Saturnus Iupiter Mars Venus; Saturnus Iupiter Mars Mercurius; Saturnus Iupiter Mars Luna; Saturnus Iupiter Sol Venus; Saturnus Iupiter Sol Mercurius; Saturnus Iupiter Sol Luna; Saturnus Iupiter Venus Mercurius; Saturnus Iupiter Venus Luna; Saturnus Iupiter Mercurius Luna; Saturnus Mars Sol Venus; Saturnus Mars Sol Mercurius; Saturnus Mars Sol Luna; Saturnus Sol Venus Mercurius; Saturnus Sol Venus Luna; Saturnus Sol mercurius Luna; Saturnus Venus Mercurius Luna; Iuppiter Mars Sol Venus; Iupiter Mars Sol Mercurius; Iupiter Mars Sol Luna; Iupiter Mars Venus Mercurius; Iupiter Mars Venus Luna; Iupiter Mars Mercurius Luna; Iuppiter Sol Venus Mercurius; Iuppiter Sol Venus Luna; Iupiter Sol Mercurius Luna; Iupiter Venus Mercurius Luna; Mars Sol Venus Mercurius; Mars Sol Venus Luna; Mars Sol Mercurius Luna; Mars Venus Mercurius Luna; Sol Venus Mercurius Luna.</p>
<p>Quinaria 21<span class="note"><a aria-label="481" class="note txt" href="#n481"></a><small class="note" data-sign="481" id="n481"> Quinaria 21<span class="txt">]</span> Quinaria 21<i class="txt"> add. i. m. V</i></small></span>: Saturnus Iupiter Mars Sol Venus; Saturnus Iupiter Mars Sol Mercurius; Saturnus Iupiter Mars Sol</p></section>